Contato

psequeiradias@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/paulodias-25441167 (LinkedIn)

Principais competências

Dispositivos médicos Biotecnologia Ciências da vida

Languages

Portuguese (Native or Bilingual) English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Paulo Dias

Healthcare Consultant

Lisboa

Resumo

2018 Abr -

2017 Abr - Senior Country Manager Portugal - Thermo

Fisher Diagnostics

2011 - 2017 Mar Iberia General Manager, ThermoFisher –

Immuno Diagnostics Division

2004 - 2011 General Manager , Phadia Portugal

2003 - 2004 Director Diagnostics Division, Pfizer Portugal

1991 - 2003 Director Diagnostics Division, Pharmacia Portugal

1985 – 1991 Director Diagnostics Division, Jaba Portugal

1984 – 1985 Product Manager, Jaba Portugal

1981 - 1984 Assistent of Bioestatistic, Faculty Medicine Lisbon

1980 - 1981 Professor Fishing Technologies, Fishing School -

Pedrouços

1978 – 1980 Researcher, Secretary of State for the Environment

Experiência

Nenhuma

Desempregado

abril de 2018 - Present (2 anos 5 meses)

Lisboa, Portugal

Private

Healthcare Consultant abril de 2018 - abril de 2018 (1 mês)

Lisboa e Região, Portugal

Nehnuma

Desempregado

abril de 2018 - abril de 2018 (1 mês)

Thermo Fisher Diagnostics Senior Country Manager abril de 2017 - 2018 (1 ano) Portugal

ThermoFisher
General Manager
março de 2011 - 2014 (3 anos)

Formação acadêmica

Universidade Nova de Lisboa (1999 - 2001)

Faculdade de Ciências da Universidade de Lisboa Licentiate degree, Biologia - Geral · (1976 - 1980)

Faculdade de Ciências da Universidade de Lisboa Licentiate degree, Biologia Marinha e Oceanografia Biológica